socialfresh.com 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: March  27, 2017**

Social Fresh is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to Social Fresh websites SocialFresh.com, SocialMediaCurrent.com, SocialFreshConference.com and governs data collection and usage of that data. By using the Social Fresh website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

#### Your Personal Information

Social Fresh collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home and/or work address and/or telephone number.

Users are under no obligation to provide such information. However, we cannot guarantee that we can provide our full services without certain user information.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Social Fresh public message boards, forums, comments, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Social Fresh does not read your private online communications with others.

Social Fresh encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Social Fresh so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Social Fresh is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Social Fresh family of websites or the use of your information by such outside websites.

#### Use of Your Personal Information

Social Fresh collects and uses your personal information to operate the Social Fresh website and deliver the services you have requested. Social Fresh may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Social Fresh and its affiliates or sponsors. Social Fresh may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services.

Social Fresh does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Social Fresh may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Social Fresh may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Social Fresh, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Social Fresh does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Social Fresh websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Social Fresh or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Social Fresh (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Social Fresh, or the public.

#### Security of your Personal Information

No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. Social Fresh uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Social Fresh secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

#### Changes to this Statement

Social Fresh will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Social Fresh encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Social Fresh is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the “Last Updated” date above.

#### Enforcement of this Privacy Statement

If you have questions regarding this statement, [contact us here](https://www.socialfresh.com/contact/). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or we have not addressed your inquiry to your satisfaction, you should then [contact us here](https://www.socialfresh.com/contact/).

#### To Unsubscribe From Social Fresh

You may unsubscribe from Social Fresh marketing communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of the company’s emails. Additionally, you may unsubscribe by [contacting Social Fresh Support here](https://www.socialfresh.com/contact/).

#### Contact Information

Social Fresh welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Social Fresh has not adhered to this Statement, please [contact Social Fresh here](https://www.socialfresh.com/contact/). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
